Angkor Wat
Visited by millions.
The reason we first came to Cambodia, and why we are still here.
Now...
Empty.
One of the worlds greatest wonders.
All left for us to explore..
Alone.
We can let our girls run around on their own.
Jump from stone to stone.
Stunning.
At the same time...
heartbreaking.
No people means no income.
No income for people with no backup.
People of Siem Reap are struggling to make ends meet.
And like so many others in the tourism industry,
Babel Guesthouse is now at risk.
Babel is just a small guesthouse, but its a guesthouse with a big heart.
We are a big family, with a lot of people depending on Babels survival.
Help us survive this crisis by DONATING. Follow this link:
https://gogetfunding.com/babelguesthouse/